<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
    xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
    xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
	<channel>
<title>News</title><link>https://press.ozcorp.io/index.html</link><description>PRESS</description><dc:language>en</dc:language><language>en</language><dc:creator>OZCORP SCIENTIFIC</dc:creator><dc:rights>&#xa9; 2023 OZCORP SCIENTIFIC LLC</dc:rights><dc:date>2024-04-22T20:58:10-04:00</dc:date><admin:generatorAgent rdf:resource="http://www.realmacsoftware.com/" />
<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
<sy:updateBase>2000-01-01T12:00+00:00</sy:updateBase>
<lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 22:42:44 -0400</lastBuildDate><item><title>Ozcorp Scientific&#x27;s portfolio venture&#x2c; GENOS&#x2c; to participate in the BioLeap Accelerator Program&#x27;s Inaugural Cohort</title><dc:creator>OZCORP SCIENTIFIC</dc:creator><category>Press</category><dc:date>2024-04-22T20:58:10-04:00</dc:date><link>https://press.ozcorp.io/files/genos-participate-bioleap-accelerator-puerto-rico.html#unique-entry-id-9</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://press.ozcorp.io/files/genos-participate-bioleap-accelerator-puerto-rico.html#unique-entry-id-9</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[GUAYNABO, PUERTO RICO &ndash; Ozcorp Scientific, a Puerto Rico based biotech venture studio, is proud to announce that GENOS, one of its recently debuted portfolio companies, has been selected to join the inaugural cohort of the BioLeap Life Science Startup Accelerator Program.  GENOS is a bioinformatics-as-a-service company providing innovative solutions to streamline research and development processes in life sciences.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Ozcorp Scientific Unveils GENOS to Propel Biotechnology Research Through Tailored Bioinformatics Services</title><dc:creator>OZCORP SCIENTIFIC</dc:creator><category>Press</category><dc:date>2024-04-18T07:00:00-04:00</dc:date><link>https://press.ozcorp.io/files/ozcorp-unveils-genos-bioinformatics-from-stealth.html#unique-entry-id-8</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://press.ozcorp.io/files/ozcorp-unveils-genos-bioinformatics-from-stealth.html#unique-entry-id-8</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[GUAYNABO, PUERTO RICO  &ndash; Ozcorp Scientific, a biotech venture studio, proudly announces the official emergence of <a href="https://genos.bio" target="_blank">GENOS</a>, marking its decisive step out of stealth-mode and into the limelight of pioneering bioinformatics solutions. Spearheaded by Dr. Osvaldo D. Rivera, a Bioinformatics Scientist and Cancer Cell Biologist, GENOS aims to revolutionize the landscape of bioinformatics services by providing accessible solutions to investigator's most complex projects and biological data hurdles. GENOS is positioned strategically within Puerto Rico, a recently designated Tech Hub to spur American innovation in biotechnologies, biopharmaceuticals and medical devices.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Ozcorp Scientific Completes Registration in Puerto Rico to Invest in the Region&#x27;s Biotech Economy and Catalyze Innovative Ventures </title><dc:creator>OZCORP SCIENTIFIC</dc:creator><category>Press</category><dc:date>2023-12-08T07:07:00-04:00</dc:date><link>https://press.ozcorp.io/files/ozcorp-scientific-completes-registration-puerto-rico-invest-biotech-catalyze-ventures%20.html#unique-entry-id-4</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://press.ozcorp.io/files/ozcorp-scientific-completes-registration-puerto-rico-invest-biotech-catalyze-ventures%20.html#unique-entry-id-4</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[GUAYNABO, PUERTO RICO &ndash; Ozcorp Scientific, a biotech venture studio, has announced the successful completion of its registration process in Puerto Rico, marking a significant milestone in the company's strategic roadmap and commitment to fostering the island's burgeoning biotech sector.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Ozcorp Scientific Debuts Comprehensive Suite of Executive Services to Empower Early-Stage Biotech Businesses</title><dc:creator>OZCORP SCIENTIFIC</dc:creator><category>Press</category><dc:date>2023-11-16T16:20:00-04:00</dc:date><link>https://press.ozcorp.io/files/ozcorp-scientific-debuts-executive-services.html#unique-entry-id-2</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://press.ozcorp.io/files/ozcorp-scientific-debuts-executive-services.html#unique-entry-id-2</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[GUAYNABO, PUERTO RICO &ndash; Ozcorp Scientific, a new force in the domain of scientific innovation, proudly announces the launch of its suite of Executive Services aimed at catalyzing growth and success within the biotech sector. With an unwavering commitment to fostering groundbreaking initiatives and driving transformative change, Ozcorp Scientific's suite of services is poised to redefine the landscape of biotech business strategies.]]></content:encoded></item></channel>
</rss>